Contact

krubsam@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kristina-rubsam-669450a8 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management Healthcare Patient Safety

Kristina Rubsam

RN

Louisville, Illinois

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the media production industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Customer Service, Physician Relations, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA). Strong healthcare services professional graduated from McKendree University.

Experience

Travel RN

RN

February 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months)

Southern Illinois

Domestic Engineer
Domestic Engineer
July 1990 - January 2019 (28 years 7 months)
Louisville, Illinois

Mobile Anesthesiologists of Southern Illinois Nurse Administrator October 2014 - February 2016 (1 year 5 months)

Clay County Hospital and Clinics Med/Surg RN September 2011 - September 2014 (3 years 1 month) Flora, Illinois

Self Employed LPN/CNA July 2007 - September 2011 (4 years 3 months) Private Care

Flora Pavilion Nursing Home and Rehabilitation Center

Page 1 of 2

Director of Medical Records January 2000 - March 2007 (7 years 3 months)

Flora, Mississippi

Education

Illinois Eastern Community Colleges-Frontier Community Coll Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

McKendree University

McKendree University Nursing